{
    "id": "c56351524d4243c18345fee1ad885d3f",
    "title": "Both, Either, Neither",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "...................... of them were ill so they stayed at home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Either",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a0edd7f58fd64e72be819ebc13b880b7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t like ..................... of these colors.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e627a2afe7144d4c88efab4c154ae56e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t decide between these gowns. I like them ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "87cae4a08995436f83e74cad5e53a46e"
        },
        {
            "question": "..................... Angelina nor Jennifer turned up today.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Neither",
                "Either"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8c5270b086a94fef9fa2ebdad23a7414"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can take ………………….. the bus or the train.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "neither",
                "both"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1b7f53d5b800412dae54e7dc1341283b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I know you don’t like me. I don’t like you …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "neither",
                "both"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "523379cf7e804b06857777e3210fd734"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. John nor Peter could solve the problem.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Neither",
                "Either",
                "Both"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "051103cd2b614cbf9927197a6fd8beaf"
        },
        {
            "question": "..................... my parents enjoy riding.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Neither",
                "Either"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d4f177c9d4c649c68aaf7ef81a7410cc"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has invited us …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "faad7706e97c4d39b4caa5381105c27f"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………… dances and sings.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f65f35e0e5b44456b83bf4902fd64071"
        }
    ]
}